Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Catherine and today we're talking about a dream home.
我是Catherine，今天我们聊的是梦想之家。
So building the home of your dreams.
也就是建造你梦想中的房子。
That's right and this lesson today is advanced so it might be a little bit hard and we're
没错，今天的课程是高级水平，所以可能有点难度，我们
going to be taking a look at not only some vocabulary related to your home or decorations
不仅会学习一些与家或装饰相关的词汇，
and stuff but also how to treat your loved one in a nice way or little nicknames.
还会学习如何用甜蜜的方式对待你的爱人，或者一些小昵称。
Cute names, pet names.
可爱的名字，爱称。
That's right.
没错。
Okay.
好的。
So stay tuned.
请继续收听。
We'll be talking about very specific things having to do with building a home and home
我们会讨论与建造房屋和房屋
remodeling.
翻新相关的非常具体的内容。
And so we'll hear this dialogue one time but when we're back in just a minute here we'll
我们会先听一遍这段对话，等我们稍后回来时，
be talking about what those things mean.
再讨论这些内容的意思。
Mr. and Mrs. Robinson, let's get straight to it.
罗宾逊先生和太太，我们直接开始吧。
You have saved up your money for years and are now ready to build your dream home.
你们攒了好多年的钱，现在准备建造梦想之家了。
What did you have in mind?
你们有什么想法？
A suburban bungalow straight out of the 60s.
一个60年代风格的郊区平房。
A perfect lawn with minimal landscaping, brick patio in the backyard with an old fashioned
一个完美的草坪，极简的景观设计，后院有砖砌露台，配一个老式
grill, quaint lawn furniture and a swimming pool.
烤架，别致的草坪家具，还有一个游泳池。
A two car carport, pastel siding and a gable roof completed with white shutters and a white
一个双车位车棚，浅色墙板，人字形屋顶，配上白色百叶窗和白色
picket fence.
尖桩篱笆。
Uh, honey?
呃，亲爱的？
In the living room we would have moss green rugs and a fireplace with a stone mantle and
客厅里我们会铺苔绿色地毯，有一个带石质壁炉架的壁炉，
wood paneling on the walls.
墙上用木板装饰。
In the kitchen the cupboards would be a pale yellow and we would have a turquoise metal
厨房的橱柜是淡黄色的，我们会有一个蓝绿色的金属
oven and vinyl flooring.
烤箱和乙烯基地板。
Um, sweetie?
嗯，甜心？
But I was thinking of more a modern style house.
但我更想要一个现代风格的房子。
An open concept house all glass, wood, metal and concrete.
一个开放式设计的房子，全是玻璃、木头、金属和混凝土。
But sweetums, there's always a lot of wasted space in those kinds of homes.
但是，亲爱的，那种房子总是有很多浪费的空间。
Besides it's just a fad.
而且那只是一时流行。
It doesn't have the homey feeling the old homes do.
它没有老房子那种温馨的感觉。
Sweetie pie, it's not a lot of wasted space.
小甜心，那不是浪费空间。
It is relaxing and the house would be eco-friendly with an in-floor heating system and designed
它很放松，而且房子会很环保，有地暖系统，设计成
to retain the heat of the sun in the winter and keep the house cool in the summer.
冬天能保留太阳的热量，夏天能保持凉爽。
We would have solar panels on the roof.
我们会在屋顶上装太阳能板。
Do you know how much those things cost?
你知道那些东西要多少钱吗？
What about your vintage furniture, dearest?
那你的复古家具怎么办，最亲爱的？
And instead of a lawn, which is also a lot of wasted space and would require environmentally
而且，与其要一个草坪——那也是浪费空间，还需要使用对环境
harmful pesticides, we would have a fish pond in the backyard and a garden that would cover
有害的杀虫剂——我们不如在后院建一个鱼塘，再有一个覆盖整个院子的花园，
the whole yard so we could grow our own food.
这样我们就可以自己种食物了。
But buttercup, I thought you always said that you loved visiting your grandmother's house.
但是，小黄花，我以为你一直说你喜欢去你奶奶家。
And I thought you, Mr. Scientist, were all up on saving the planet with your technological
而且我以为你，科学家先生，一直热衷于用你的技术
advancement.
进步来拯救地球。
Um, well, I am just going to get some coffee while you two keep discussing.
嗯，好吧，我去倒杯咖啡，你们俩继续讨论。
Alright we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So apparently the couple can't seem to agree.
显然这对夫妻似乎无法达成一致。
He wants something different than what she does and in the end I think they were a little
他想要的和她想要的不一样，最后我觉得他们都有点
bit irritated with each other.
互相生气了。
Doesn't this always happen though?
但这不是经常发生吗？
I mean my dream home is probably not your dream home.
我的意思是，我的梦想之家可能不是你的梦想之家。
I don't know, it's weird.
我不知道，这很奇怪。
But I mean you would probably have to, I don't know, compensate somehow or...
但我觉得你可能得，我不知道，妥协一下或者……
Well that's the beauty of compromise I think.
嗯，我觉得这就是妥协的美妙之处。
You can go back and forth but with your loved one or your spouse you have to make some decisions
你们可以来回商量，但和你的爱人或配偶在一起，你必须做出一些决定，
about what you want and what they want.
关于你想要什么和他们想要什么。
All you need to do is give a guy his own room in which he can decorate and do whatever he
你只需要给一个男人他自己的房间，他可以在里面装饰，做任何他
wants with it.
想做的事。
That's all you need.
这就够了。
You mean you.
你是说你吧。
No, no, not me.
不，不，不是我。
You want to decorate the house in any way you want, fine.
你想怎么装饰房子都行，没问题。
But just give us one room, you know, like five meters by five meters where we can put
但给我们一个房间，你知道，比如五米乘五米，我们可以放
anything we want.
任何我们想要的东西。
A beer cooler, a TV, a PS3, a sound system, and a couple guitars.
一个啤酒冷却器、一台电视、一台PS3、一套音响，还有几把吉他。
Yeah, probably, yeah, yeah.
是啊，大概吧，对对。
Yeah.
对。
That's enough.
这就够了。
You described it.
你描述出来了。
I've been to your house, I know.
我去过你家，我知道。
Anyway, we've got a lot of great words here in Language Takeaway so let's take a peek
不管怎样，我们在“语言要点”里有很多好词，让我们来看看
at some of those.
其中的一些。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
All right.
好的。
So the first word that we have or it's actually a concept, minimal landscaping.
所以我们的第一个词，或者说是一个概念，是“极简景观设计”。
Okay, so minimal is a style, minimalist actually.
好的，“极简”是一种风格，实际上是“极简主义”。
And minimal landscaping is this kind of style of, well, designing your lawn or your garden.
而“极简景观设计”是一种设计你的草坪或花园的风格。
So minimal means not having adornments or decorations.
所以“极简”意味着没有装饰或点缀。
Okay.
好的。
So it's kind of like the less is more type thing.
所以这有点像“少即是多”那种理念。
Exactly.
没错。
So minimal architecture could be very simple, lots of clean lines, not much decoration.
所以极简建筑可以非常简单，有很多干净的线条，装饰不多。
It's the opposite of something that's baroque and highly ornamented.
这与巴洛克风格和高度装饰的东西相反。
And I don't like that.
我不喜欢那种风格。
I'm into minimal.
我喜欢极简风格。
All right, minimalist.
好吧，极简主义者。
Anyways, we have minimal landscaping.
总之，我们有极简景观设计。
And while he's talking about his patio and an old fashioned grill, and he said quaint
当他谈到他的露台和一个老式烤架时，他说了“古雅”
lawn furniture.
的草坪家具。
Quaint is sometimes, well, it's usually kind of a bad thing.
“古雅”有时，嗯，通常不是什么好事。
We say something is quaint in the way of saying that it's cute, but we don't really like it
我们说某样东西“古雅”，有点像说它可爱，但我们并不真的喜欢它，
because it's maybe old fashioned or kind of old style.
因为它可能过时了或者风格老旧。
So oh, isn't that quaint?
所以，哦，那不是挺古雅的吗？
It's something that people from the city often say about people in the country, at least
这通常是城里人对乡下人说的话，至少
in America.
在美国是这样。
So, oh, because you know, I went to school on the East Coast and I'm from the Midwest.
所以，哦，因为你知道，我在东海岸上学，而我来自中西部。
So people on the East Coast would say, oh, your house is so quaint, small and cute and
所以东海岸的人会说，哦，你的房子真古雅，又小又可爱又
old fashioned because they live in a big fancy New York apartment or whatever.
老式，因为他们住在纽约那种大而豪华的公寓里。
So quaint is usually something that's not the nicest.
所以“古雅”通常不是什么好词。
So he's looking for some lawn furniture that's not like plastic or new.
所以他在找一些不是塑料或新的草坪家具。
It's more like old fashioned, maybe wood.
更像是老式的，也许是木头的。
Right.
对。
And kind of traditional and not fancy.
而且比较传统，不花哨。
Kind of simple.
比较简单。
Now, he's also talking about the house and he wants, well, a two carport, pastel siding
现在，他也在谈论房子，他想要一个双车位车棚、柔和色调的墙板
and a gable roof.
和一个人字形屋顶。
So now we know what a roof is, but what is a gable roof?
所以我们现在知道屋顶是什么，但什么是人字形屋顶？
A gable is a thing, right?
人字形是一种结构，对吧？
And it's almost like an extension of the roof in certain parts.
它有点像屋顶在某些部分的延伸。
For example, on a traditional Cape Cod style house, you have windows in the front that
例如，在传统的科德角风格房子上，前面有窗户，
they're not a part of the roof.
它们不是屋顶的一部分。
They're an extension.
它们是延伸出来的。
They come out.
它们凸出来。
They're kind of popping out like eyes.
它们有点像眼睛一样突出来。
Exactly.
没错。
They're coming out like eyes.
它们像眼睛一样凸出来。
And so the roof, obviously you need a roof on top of those windows.
所以屋顶，显然你需要在那些窗户上面有个屋顶。
So that kind of roof, that little extension, that's called a gable.
所以那种屋顶，那个小延伸部分，就叫人字形。
And so there's a wonderful book that's famous in American history called The House of Seven
所以有一本在美国历史上著名的书叫《七角楼》。
Gables.
That means that on this roof of the house, there are seven different parts that come
意思是这房子的屋顶上有七个不同的部分凸
out.
出来。
Seven gables.
七个人字形。
It's very unique.
非常独特。
Those houses usually look a little bit scary.
那些房子通常看起来有点吓人。
They do.
确实。
Victorian and imposing.
维多利亚风格且气势逼人。
All right.
好吧。
So you have a gable roof.
所以你有一个人字形屋顶。
Now you have shutters and a white picket fence.
现在你有百叶窗和一个白色尖桩篱笆。
This is typical.
这是典型的。
Everyone talks about a white picket fence around their house.
每个人都在谈论他们房子周围的白色尖桩篱笆。
That's right.
没错。
There was even a TV show in America years ago called Picket Fences.
美国多年前甚至有一个电视节目叫《尖桩篱笆》。
And I think a picket fence is kind of this ideal in American culture about having your
我认为尖桩篱笆是美国文化中的一种理想，代表着在郊区拥有自己的房子
own home in the suburbs and having your own space.
和自己的空间。
And so around your yard, around your garden, you have this white picket fence.
所以在你的院子周围，你的花园周围，你有这个白色尖桩篱笆。
And so a picket is, I think, the pointed part.
而“尖桩”我想是指尖的部分。
So a picket fence is thin pieces of wood that stand in the ground and are connected to protect
所以尖桩篱笆是由细木条立在地上并连接起来，用来保护
your property from other people coming inside.
你的财产不让别人进来。
Okay.
好的。
So that's a white picket fence.
所以那就是白色尖桩篱笆。
You'll hear it all the time.
你会经常听到它。
Usually in movies or in TV shows, they talk about having their own little house with their
通常在电影或电视节目中，他们会谈论拥有自己的小房子，带着
dog and a white picket fence.
狗和白色尖桩篱笆。
Exactly.
没错。
Two kids, two cars.
两个孩子，两辆车。
And a white picket fence.
和一个白色尖桩篱笆。
All right.
好吧。
So now the woman argued that she wanted something a little bit more modern.
所以现在那位女士争辩说她想要更现代一点的东西。
And well, the guy said, you know what?
而那个男人说，你知道吗？
It's just wasted space.
那只是浪费空间。
And those types of homes are just a fad.
那种房子只是一时流行。
A fad.
一时流行。
So a fad is something that is passing.
所以“一时流行”是指短暂的东西。
It's something that's popular for a short time, but then it goes away.
它是短时间内流行，但然后就会消失的东西。
It's not popular anymore.
它不再流行了。
Right.
对。
So...
那么...
For example, I think for a while, remember those shoes that used to have little red lights
比如说，我想了一会儿，还记得那些鞋后跟带小红灯的鞋子吗？
in the back and the heel?
就是鞋后跟和鞋底有小红灯的那种？
Oh yeah.
哦，对。
LA lights.
LA Lights（洛杉矶之光）。
Those were a fad.
那是一种风潮。
It was really popular for like a year.
大概流行了一年左右。
Everyone had them, everyone wore them, and then they just went away.
每个人都有一双，每个人都穿，然后它们就消失了。
One of my favorite fads of the 1980s were those shirts that would change color if the
我最喜欢的80年代风潮之一是那些会随室温变色的T恤，
room temperature changed color.
如果室温变化，颜色也会变。
So if you go outside and it's hot, they would become bright pink.
所以如果你到外面热的地方，它们会变成亮粉色。
But if you're in a cold room, they would go blue and green.
但如果你在冷房间里，它们会变成蓝色和绿色。
It was really fun, but they're definitely out of fashion these days.
那真的很有趣，但如今肯定过时了。
Yeah, I don't think they wear them anymore.
是啊，我觉得现在没人穿它们了。
So that's a fad.
所以那就是一种风潮。
Something that's temporary.
一种短暂的东西。
It's popular for a while.
它流行一阵子。
So he called her house a fad and she says, well, what about your house?
所以他说她的房子是一种风潮，然后她说，那你的房子呢？
All this vintage furniture.
所有这些复古家具。
What's vintage?
什么是复古？
Vintage?
复古？
Well, some people think that vintage is a fad.
嗯，有些人觉得复古只是一时流行。
A lot of people really enjoy buying vintage furniture or vintage clothing.
很多人真的很喜欢买复古家具或复古服装。
Vintage means old.
复古就是旧的意思。
Old.
旧。
It's a nice way of saying old or like a nice or cool way of saying old.
这是一种说“旧”的好听方式，或者说是一种时髦、酷的说法。
Yeah.
对。
So it's almost like, for example, right now, 1940s and 50s clothes are very popular.
所以差不多就像，比如说，现在1940年代和50年代的衣服很流行。
A lot of girls are into this kind of style.
很多女孩喜欢这种风格。
So it's called vintage clothing because it's not from today's styles.
所以它被称为复古服装，因为它不是当今的款式。
It's an old style.
它是一种旧风格。
Or you could even call those big flowing dresses from the 1970s vintage clothing.
或者你甚至可以把1970年代那些宽大飘逸的裙子称为复古服装。
So vintage furniture would be furniture that comes from a different time, a different era,
所以复古家具就是来自不同时代、不同年代的家具，
and it's popular now.
而且现在很流行。
Right.
没错。
They're popular now.
它们现在很流行。
Or people like to buy them now.
或者人们现在喜欢买它们。
That's right.
说得对。
So they're special because they come from a different time.
所以它们很特别，因为它们来自不同的时代。
Okay.
好的。
So those are the words that we have for today on Language Takeaway.
这些就是我们今天在“语言小贴士”环节学到的单词。
Why don't we move on now to some pet names or some sweet ways that you can call your
现在我们不妨进入“流利度训练”环节，聊聊一些爱称或甜蜜的称呼方式，用来称呼你的
loved ones on Fluency Builder.
爱人。
Fluency Builder.
流利度训练。
So the reason this dialogue is very funny is because we have these two people who are
这段对话之所以很有趣，是因为这两个人
clearly in disagreement about the kinds of furniture and house they want, but they're
明显对家具和房子的喜好有分歧，但他们
being so nice to each other.
对彼此却非常温柔。
They have these cute names for each other.
他们互相用可爱的昵称称呼对方。
So it's really funny.
所以真的很好笑。
It almost seems like they're newlyweds, but apparently they've been saving up their entire
看起来他们就像新婚夫妇，但显然他们攒了一辈子的钱。
life.
一辈子。
So maybe they're just one of those really loving couples.
所以也许他们就是那种特别恩爱的夫妻。
Oh, Sweetums, Cutie Pie, Cutie.
哦，甜心，小可爱，宝贝。
All right.
好了。
So that's the first one.
这是第一个。
Sweetums.
甜心。
So obviously the main part of this word is sweet.
很明显这个词的主体部分是“甜”。
Sweetum, Sweetums.
甜心，甜心。
And this is a way to say, hey, sweetie.
这是一种表达方式，意思是“嘿，亲爱的”。
Sweetums.
甜心宝贝。
So you can say sweetie or sweetums.
所以你可以说“亲爱的”或“甜心宝贝”。
Exactly.
没错。
So that's a nice way of saying somebody.
这是一种称呼别人的亲切方式。
Or you can go sweetie pie.
或者你可以说“甜心派”。
Sweetie pie.
甜心派。
So pie is a food.
派是一种食物。
It's like a dessert.
就像甜点一样。
Pie is sweet.
派是甜的。
It's a sweet.
它是一种甜食。
So sweetie pie.
所以是“甜心派”。
Or you could say honey pie.
或者你可以说“蜜糖派”。
Honey pie, sweetie pie.
蜜糖派，甜心派。
So these are all cute.
这些都很可爱。
And the nice thing about these kind of pet names, these cute names, is you can change
这类昵称、可爱称呼的好处是，你可以随意改变它们，
them if you want and they're yours.
而且它们是你专属的。
So you could say honey pie, sugar bun.
所以你可以说“蜜糖派”、“糖包子”。
They're silly, but there's no real rule.
它们有点傻气，但并没有真正的规则。
But these are the most common.
但这些是最常见的。
Right.
没错。
Sweetums and sweetie pie.
Sweetums 和 sweetie pie。
Sweetie pie.
Sweetie pie。
Okay.
好的。
Now, moving on to something a little bit maybe more formal.
现在，我们来说说稍微正式一点的称呼。
Dearest.
Dearest。
This makes me think of my grandparents.
这让我想起我的祖父母。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
Dearest.
Dearest。
So dearest comes from dear.
所以 dearest 来自 dear。
Dearest is the most dear.
Dearest 是最亲爱的意思。
So someone who's the most important to you.
也就是对你来说最重要的人。
Okay.
好的。
And so you could say mummy dearest, mother dearest.
所以你可以说 mummy dearest，mother dearest。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
You heard that somewhere?
你在哪儿听到过吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Do people call their mothers like mother dearest?
人们会叫他们的妈妈 mother dearest 吗？
Mother dearest.
Mother dearest。
No, it's very 1930s.
不，那是很 1930 年代的叫法。
I'm so arrogant.
我太自大了。
Well, it's an old time thing.
嗯，那是老派的东西。
We do not say this anymore, but you can say, you know, dearest, would you mind moving the
我们现在不这么说了，但你可以说，比如，dearest，你能挪一下
car?
车吗？
I like the accent.
我喜欢这个口音。
You're kind of like English.
你有点像英国人。
All right.
好吧。
And the last one, buttercup.
最后一个，buttercup。
This is really popular.
这个真的很流行。
It's really popular.
真的很流行。
And you've heard this in a song before.
你以前在歌里听过。
You want to sing the song?
你想唱那首歌吗？
No, you sing the song.
不，你唱那首歌。
Why do you build me up?
你为什么把我捧起来？
Buttercup, baby.
Buttercup，宝贝。
Okay.
好的。
So that was in a lot of movies.
所以那在很多电影里出现过。
The word is buttercup.
这个词是 buttercup。
Also in the movie, the princess bride was the character of Princess Buttercup.
还有在电影《公主新娘》里，有个角色叫 Buttercup 公主。
And so this is a sweet, you know, obviously a sweet thing.
所以这是一个甜蜜的，你知道，显然是个甜蜜的东西。
I think a buttercup is a flower.
我觉得 buttercup 是一种花。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
Yeah.
是的。
And so these are all words you can use, names you could use with men and women, but buttercup
所以这些都是你可以用的词，可以用在男人和女人身上的名字，但 buttercup
is mostly women.
主要是用在女人身上。
I think the other ones are more general.
我觉得其他的更通用一些。
But do you think like, do guys say to their loved ones like, sweetum, sweetie pie?
但你觉得，男人会对他们的爱人说像 sweetum、sweetie pie 这样的词吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Yeah?
是吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
All right.
好吧。
So I guess guys, if you want to be really sweet and you want to win over the hearts
所以我想，男人们，如果你们想表现得特别甜蜜，想赢得
of the ladies, you can use these words as well.
女士们的心，也可以用这些词。
Another popular one is babe, which is more of a young person thing to say.
另一个流行的词是 babe，这更像是年轻人说的。
Yeah, I think it's more modern as well.
是的，我觉得也更现代一些。
Honey or babe?
Honey 还是 babe？
Baby.
Baby。
You're verging on not so sweet.
你有点不太甜蜜了。
Yeah, but like, hey, baby, how are you?
是的，但像，嘿，宝贝，你好吗？
It's like, nice.
这还不错。
But not like, hey, baby.
但不是像，嘿，宝贝。
All right.
好吧。
Well, we're going to leave you with that thought and go listen to this dialogue one more time.
嗯，我们就留给你们这个想法，再去听一遍这段对话。
We'll be back in a moment.
我们一会儿就回来。
Mr. and Mrs. Robinson, let's get straight to it.
罗宾逊先生和太太，我们直接开始吧。
You have saved up your money for years and are now ready to build your dream home.
你们攒了好多年的钱，现在准备建造你们的梦想之家。
What did you have in mind?
你们有什么想法？
A suburban bungalow straight out of the 60s.
一个 60 年代风格的郊区平房。
A perfect lawn with minimal landscaping, a brick patio in the backyard with an old-fashioned
一个完美的草坪，极少的景观设计，后院有一个砖砌露台，配着老式
grill, quaint lawn furniture, and a swimming pool.
烤架、古雅的草坪家具和一个游泳池。
A two-car carport, pastel siding, and a gable roof, completed with white shutters and a
一个双车位车棚，浅色墙板，人字形屋顶，配上白色百叶窗和
white picket fence.
白色尖桩篱笆。
Uh, honey?
呃，亲爱的？
In the living room, we would have moss green rugs and a fireplace with a stone mantle and
在客厅里，我们要苔绿色地毯，一个带石壁炉架的壁炉，
wood paneling on the walls.
墙上镶着木板。
In the kitchen, the cupboards would be a pale yellow, and we would have a turquoise metal
在厨房里，橱柜是淡黄色的，我们要一个蓝绿色的金属
oven and vinyl flooring.
烤箱和乙烯基地板。
Um, sweetie, but I was thinking of more a modern-style house, an open-concept house
嗯，亲爱的，但我想要的是更现代风格的房子，开放式设计的那种。
all glass, wood, metal, and concrete.
全是玻璃、木头、金属和混凝土。
But sweetums, there's always a lot of wasted space in those kinds of homes.
但是甜心，那种房子总是有很多浪费的空间。
Besides, it's just a fad.
再说了，那只是一时流行。
It doesn't have the homey feeling the old homes do.
它没有老房子那种温馨的感觉。
Sweetie pie, it's not a lot of wasted space.
小甜心，那不是浪费空间。
It is relaxing, and the house would be eco-friendly with an in-floor heating system and designed
它很放松，而且房子会环保，配有地暖系统，设计成
to retain the heat of the sun in the winter and keep the house cool in the summer.
冬天能保留太阳的热量，夏天让房子保持凉爽。
We would have solar panels on the roof.
我们可以在屋顶装太阳能板。
Do you know how much those things cost?
你知道那些东西要花多少钱吗？
What about your vintage furniture, dearest?
那你的复古家具怎么办，亲爱的？
And instead of a lawn, which is also a lot of wasted space and would require environmentally
而且，与其要草坪——那也是浪费空间，还需要对环境
harmful pesticides, we would have a fish pond in the backyard and a garden that would cover
有害的杀虫剂——我们可以在后院建一个鱼塘，还有一个花园，覆盖
the whole yard so we could grow our own food.
整个院子，这样我们就能自己种食物了。
But Buttercup, I thought you always said that you loved visiting your grandmother's house.
但是金凤花，我以为你一直说你喜欢去你奶奶家。
And I thought you, Mr. Scientist, were all up on saving the planet with your technological
而且我以为你，科学家先生，一直热衷于用你的技术
advancements.
进步来拯救地球。
Um, well, I am just going to get some coffee while you two keep discussing.
嗯，好吧，我去拿点咖啡，你们俩继续讨论。
Alright we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So apart from this decorations and stuff, do you agree with the vintage home, the more
所以除了这些装饰之类的东西，你同意复古风格的家，更
like minimalist thing, or do you like the open concept one, the bigger one?
像极简主义那种，还是喜欢开放式概念，更大的那种？
I love the look of minimalism, but as a place to live, it's not comfortable.
我喜欢极简主义的外观，但作为居住的地方，它不舒服。
And so when I think of an aesthetic that I like, a look that I like, I really like kind
所以当我想到我喜欢的美学、喜欢的外观时，我真的很喜欢那种
of dark wood, velvety, 19th century kind of, I think of old Vienna.
深色木头、天鹅绒、19世纪风格，让我想起老维也纳。
You like Castle Dracula.
你喜欢德古拉城堡。
No, not dark.
不，不是暗黑。
I like things to be open.
我喜欢开放的空间。
And I like a lot of natural light, but I also like oversized kind of heavy furniture and
而且我喜欢很多自然光，但我也喜欢超大号的厚重家具和
really luscious fabrics and things like that.
非常华丽的布料之类的东西。
So that's my...
所以那是我的……
I'm actually completely different because I do like this open concept.
我其实完全相反，因为我确实喜欢这种开放式概念。
I like those houses that, I like the way they look inside as well as outside when they're
我喜欢那些房子，我喜欢它们内部和外部的外观，当它们
kind of squared, big windows, clean lines.
是那种方方正正、大窗户、线条简洁的样子。
Inside is like, for example, in the kitchen you have polished aluminum or polished steel
内部比如，在厨房里，你有抛光铝或抛光钢
furniture in the kitchen, as well as a lot of white and red or black, especially.
家具，还有很多白色和红色或黑色，尤其是。
I kind of like that kind of open spaces.
我有点喜欢那种开放空间。
Primary colors.
原色。
Yeah, yeah.
对，对。
Flat screen TVs on the wall and stuff like that.
墙上的平板电视之类的东西。
Remote controls.
遥控器。
Ikea lamps.
宜家灯具。
Yeah, you know, like those remote controls where you can open your curtains, your TV
是啊，你知道，就像那些遥控器，可以同时打开窗帘、电视
and the lights all at the same time.
和灯。
I kind of like that stuff.
我有点喜欢那些东西。
Cool.
酷。
Well, let us know what you guys like because everyone has their own opinion on what a beautiful
好了，告诉我们你们喜欢什么，因为每个人对什么是美丽的
house is.
房子都有自己的看法。
And if you have any pictures, feel free to share them with us on our website, EnglishPod.com.
如果你们有照片，欢迎在我们的网站 EnglishPod.com 上分享。
All right.
好的。
We'll see you guys there.
我们那里见。
Bye.
再见。
language
语言